Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Audiovisual Collection
1949-2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0084
207.25 item(s)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Chose the appropriate language that matches the level you are describing:
For Collection: Organized into [number] series: [list series titles]
For Series or Subseries: If the series has subseries use the same format as the Collection note to state the titles of the subseries
Series: Arranged [alphabetically, chronologically, etc.]
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from IBT.
MMS ID Number
99186221324304107
- LP Collection, 1949-1982; Series 1; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 standard flat box and 1 slim LP box
  Arrangement
  Items in this series have been arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains 12", 10", and 7" LPs created between the dates of 1949 - 1982.
  - Don Leace Sings "Which Side are You On?" an old union song Side A, Don Leace Sings "Jimmy Hoffa is the Man words and music by H.J. Hicks, 7-inch LP, 2 copies, 1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamster 19th Convention, "Teamster's Song" Johnny Desmond & Orchestra Side A, "September Song" Johnny Desmond & Orchestra Side B, 7-inch LP, Produced by Sam Berger, July 1966; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Hoffa's Blues" Side A, "Teamsters Holiday" Side B 7-inch LP, 5 copies, 1966; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Augie Tried" Russ Marks and Don Carroll Side A,"Watson Road Weekend" Russ Marks and Don Carroll, 7-inch LP, Cadde, 1973; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Jimmy" Stereo Side A, "Jimmy" Mono Side B, Bob O'Donnell, 7-inch LP, Warner Bros. Records, 1975; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - AFL Convention, Sides 1 and 2, 10-inch LP, united Recording Artists, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AFL Convention, Sides 3 and 4, Sides 5 and 6, 10-inch LP, United Recording Artists, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AFL Convention, Sides 7 and 8, 10-inch LP, United Recording Artists, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Drive for Victory", Democratic Republican Independent Voter Education, Audio Section Flip Chart, 10-inch LP, 2 copies, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Glory, Glory to the Teamsters" Sammy Watkins' Orchestra and Chorus, 10-inch LP, 1962; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "What I Would Say," address by Dave Beck Part 1 and Part 3, Part2 and Part 4, 10-inch LP, Linden Vinylite Records, July 23, 1949; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters "10 Second Spots, All Cuts Identical" J. Hoffa Record #3, 12-inch LP, Air-tone Sound and Recording Company, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters "10 Second Spots, Cuts 1&2 Identical, 3&4 Identical, 5&6 Identical, 7&8 Identical" J. Hoffa, 12-inch LP, Air-tone Sound and Recording Company, April 22, 1963; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters "Cuts 1&2 - 1 minute, 3 to 8 - 10 seconds" J. Hoffa, 12-inch LP, Air-tone Sound and Recording Company, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - D13-6, Side 1 and Side 26, 12-inch LP, Central Recording Co., Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamster Special Events Report "The Dangers of the Kennedy-Ervin Bill", James R. Hoffa in an address to Joint Council 73, Part 1 and Part 2, 12-inch LP, June 10, 1959; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Joe Glazer sings Labor Songs, Part 1: "Organizing Medley", "Hold the Fort", "Joe Hill", "Union Maid", "Casey Jones", "Which Side Are You On?", "The Mill Was Made of Marble"; Part 2: "Solidarity Forever", "Automation", "Hard Times in the Mill", "Look for the Union Label", "John Henry", "Too Old to Work", "Union Buster"; 12-inch LP, Collector Records, unopened, 1982; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "Speech by James R. Hoffa", Side 1 and Side 3, 12-inch LP, Techniconic Studios, Inc, December 15, 1966; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Campaigns, Educational videos, Promotions, Rallies, Safety videos and Other Miscellaneous Videos, Series 3
  - Actions Speak Louder Than Words, ND (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Format of Original Media
    VHS
  - Union With A Heart (Silent Film, Black and White, 4 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Better Schools for a Better America (14 Minutes and 20 Seconds) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Film
  - Union With A Heart (18 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Coney Island Rally Tape 1, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Coney Island Rally Tape 2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Port Truckers' Rally Tape 1 (2 Copies), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - We Voted "YES" (30 Minutes), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Senator Wayne Morse Reports from Washington (28 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Brewer's Heritage (20 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Day in the Life of Our Drivers, ND (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Labor's Committee For Kennedy and Johnson: Kennedy Speaks to Labor (14 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Paychecks, Prices, and Prosperity (14 Minutes and 34 Seconds) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Parliamentary Procedure (23 Minutes and 25 Seconds) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brewery Worker's Strike (11 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Senator Wayne Morse Reports from Washington (26 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters: Dignity and Strength (20 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Proud to Be a Teamster Casette Tape (two copies), 1986; IBT0084 (Box SHARED box 29, Folder 8)
  - Americans at Work (14 Minutes and 44 Seconds) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Death Trap on Wheels (10 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Changing Congress: Pressure and Persuasion (15 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Drive Dinner (15 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Meet the Press (28 Minutes, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Drive Campaigns (5 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Truck Safety (60 Seconds) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Charity Fight" R-2 KPLR TV (Black and White) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Proud to be a Teamster (4 minutes) and We're America's Teamsters (24 minutes) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - What You Say Matters (15 Minutes), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Pressure: Teamsters Take On Rite Aid!, ND (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Project Rise Video (11 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Justice at Diamond Walnut (Box 4, Item 5)
  - Teamsters Rally Columbus, Ohio Tape 1, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Teamsters Rally Columbus, Ohio Tape 2, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Teamsters Rally Columbus, Ohio Tape 3, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters MPLS Rally Tape 1, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters MPLS Rally Tape 2, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Teamsters/Walnut EXT. RALLY- No Agribusiness Rally, Mariachi Band, Carly Speech, Delores Huerta Speech, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Special Events Report "The Dangers of The Kennedy-Ervin Bill" by James Hoffa in an Address to Joint Council 73, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Teamsters- Casino Rama Rally with James Hoffa Tape 2, ND (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Unase A La Familia De Los Teamsters, Teamsters Local 25, ND (Box 4, Item 2)
  - IBT Marketing Video Loop, 2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Whatever It Takes: The 2002 UPS Contract (16 minutes), Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Dallas Cross Border Rally, Mexican Truck Rally, 2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Casino Rama Rally with James Hoffa Tape 1, ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - "Half a Job is Not Enough" Rallies News Clips SF, Rockford IL, Louisville, NY Local 804, 1997; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Teamsters Rally Las Vegas, NV Tape 2, 2002; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - House Calls: Organizing Department, Teamsters Union (24 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - IBT Non-Traditional Women's PSA, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Work Ahead (13 Minutes and 25 Seconds) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Wisconsin Story (16 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "Seattle" Milk Delivery - War Bonds (Black and White with Sound) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - IBT "Non-Traditional Women's PSA" (30 Seconds), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Turn it Around: Teamster Stewards Solving Problems on the Job (17 Minutes), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Babson Bros. Patent 2709416, ND (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - HBO Hoffa Project NTR Rally- IBT Crew DC, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Railroads: End of the Line? (25 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Carrier or Killer? (32 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Sending Them A Message: Teamsters Take on the Special Interests (12 Minutes) (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - IBT Port Division Loop, ND (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - We the People Flood Story, ND (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Food Chains: The Revolution in America's Fields, Educational Edition, 2014 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - Teamsters Truck Border-Crossing, Fox 6 News San Diego and MSNBC News Live MSNBC NATIONAL, 2007 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - A Bench in the Park, ND (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Teamsters Canada Growing Together, ND (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - One Strike and You're Out! (15 minutes), Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Happy Returns, ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Our Decision. Our Future., ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - "It's Our Contract: We'll Fight For It!" (4 minutes), 1997; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - "It's Our Contract: We'll Fight For It!" (4 minutes), 1997; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Union With A Heart (20 minutes), ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Where Were You? (26 Minutes), ND (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Gibbons Interviewing Zeckendorf KWK-TV RE: Mill Creek Redevelopment (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Paris Photos Larchmont, 1996; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    DVD
  - Time for Unity IBT (11:19 minutes), ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - A Message to the I.B. of T. Delegates: Make Your Vote Count (10 minutes), ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Teamster Women on the Move (6 minutes), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - United We Win IBT Carhaul Contract Campaign, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Organizing Teamsters Rock Vegas Rally America West/Clark County Org, 2002; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Turn it Around: Teamsters Stewards Solving Problems on the Job (17 minutes) (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand in Hand (6 minutes), 1996; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - SF #18 Pre-Ratification Meeting, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - SF #19 Hayward- Cutaways- Pre-Ratification Meeting, Beginning of Meeting, Rome Speaking, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - SF #20 Hayward- Beginning of Ratification Meeting, Interview with Nurses Outside Bowling Alley, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - SF #21 Interview Hawthorne- Nurses Outside Bowling Alley, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - SF #23 Voting- Ratification of Contract, World Airways -3 Flight Attendants, Wanda Walking Down Terminal, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - "Charity Fight" R-1, KLPR TV - B&W, ND; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - "Better World" Harold Gibbons, ND; Series 1 (Box 2, Item 24)
  - Portland Newspaper Strike, Series 1 (Box 2, Item 25)
  - Viewpoint with Harold Gibbons, ND (Box 2, Item 27)
  - LA #2 El Segundo, Fire Station, Drills with Water, Men Putting on Equipment, Interview with George Lewis in Front of Fire Truck, 1985 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - LA #3 Interview with George Lewis Standing by Firetruck, 1st Part of Interview with Dan Seward Inside Firehouse, Firemen Sitting on Table, 1985 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - LA #4 Interview with Dan Seward at Firehouse, Painters on the Lot, Painters on the Street- Stop Sign, Interview with Painters by their Truck, 1985 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - LA #5 Redondo Beach, Interview with Tony, Painters Working on the Street, Tony and Mark Taking Equipment Off Truck, Beginning of Interview with Share, Dispatcher in Hawthorne, 1985 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - LA #6 Hawthorne- South Bay Community Center, Shari- Dispatcher, 1985 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - LA #7 Interview with Shari- Dispatcher, 1985 (Box 3, Item 6)
  - LA #8 Hawthorne- South Bay Community Center, Allene- Supervisor Interview, Working on a Call w/ a Dispatcher, Santa Monica, Bill Pierson- Bus Driver, 1985 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - LA #9 Santa Monica Interview, William Pierson- Bus Driver, 1985 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - LA #10 Santa Monica Interviews, Bill Pierson- Bus Driver, George Santos- Federal Employee and Policeman, 1985 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - LA #11 Santa Monica Interviews, George Santos- Federal Employee and Policeman, Wes Thompson- Street Cleaner, 1985 (Box 3, Item 10)
  - LA #12 Santa Monica, Ruben- Gardner, Tom Moore- Sanitation Truck, San Gabriel- Marilyn Steinhardt, Cafeteria in Jefferson School, 1985 (Box 3, Item 11)
  - LA #13 Santa Gabriel, Cutaways of Marilyn in Jefferson School Cafeteria, Minnie- Janitor- Jefferson School, San Gabriel- Betty Dykes- Teacher's Aide, 1985 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - LA #14 San Gabriel- Wilson School- Esparanza, Cutaways with Kids Reading, Pasadena- Ray- A Welder, 1985 (Box 3, Item 13)
  - LA #15 Pasadena- Ray Martin, Welder/Metal Worker, 1985 (Box 3, Item 14)
  - IBT Centennial Celebration Video (1 hour and 39 minutes), 2003 (Box 3, Item 36)
  - The Teamsters vs. PFAA "Teamsters Local 2000 or PFA- The Decision is Yours" (10 minutes), 2003 (Box 3, Item 45)
  - Teamsters "A Strong Legacy, A Powerful Future", 2003 (Box 3, Item 46)
  - High Alert" Teamster Rail Conference High Alert News Clips (10 minutes and 35 seconds) (Box 3, Item 50)
  - The Harry Bridges Project Presents To Make a Long Story Short: The Life and Times of Sam Kagel, 2007 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - Putting the Members First, Facts About the Vote on Teamster Strike Benefits and Programs to Win Good Contracts, 1994; Series 2 (Box 7, Box 1)
  - IBT UPS: "Whatever it Takes" Rough Cut, Parcel-UPS 2002 Contract Negotiations, April 23, 2002; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IBT UPS 2002: "Whatever it Takes", May 10, 2002; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - IBT UPS 2002 "Whatever it Takes", Final Rough Cut, April 25, 2002; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - IBT Diamond Walnut 14 Years on the Line, BETA cassette, May 16, 2006; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - UPS Freight Truck Shots #2A, BETA cassette, February 26, 2006; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Justice at Diamond Walnut," Featuring music by Bruce Springsteen, 2006; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 2004 City Strike Tape 1, August 7-17, 2004; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 2004 City Strike, Tape 2, August 7-17, 2004; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - City 8, June 1997; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "No Mob Rule! The 1996 Teamster Convention", August 1996; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "A Decade of Dignity: Teamsters Meeting the Challenge", 1986; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - "Two Nations - One Union", 1996; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "Teamsters: A Changing Union In a Changing World", 1993; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Glen Pearcy Productions Teamsters, "Every Member an Organizer", July 5, 1996; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - "Roadmap for Skills for Tomorrow: A Young Person's Guide to Union Careers", ND; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - "Labors Turning Point", ND; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Teamster Network Introductions, Frank D. Fitzsimmons, Professional Broadcast Tape, March 3, 1978; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - "Crime, INC.", April 3, 1987; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - "An Oral Historian's Work" with University of Maine Folklore Professor Edward D. (Sandy) Ives, 1987; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Crime INC.: The Mob at Work, Mob Hits Unions", 1984; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "A Conversation with Richard Wilbur," Poet Laureate, Grace Cavalieri, ND; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Alex Drier Teamsters I and II, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - American Standoff [1st copy], 2002 June 10; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Americans for a Fair Chance: "Talking About Affirmative Action.", 1998 September 15; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - American Standoff [2nd copy], 2002 June 10; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - As Long As It Takes: Overnight 2000 [1st copy], 2000 January 26; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - American Standoff [3rd copy], 2002 June 10; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - As Long As It Takes: Overnight 2000 [2nd copy], 2000 January 26; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - At the River I Stand [1st copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - At the River I Stand [2nd copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [1st copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [2nd copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [3rd copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [4th copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [5th copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [6th copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [7th copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Battle in Seattle, RT: 18:55 [8th copy], Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - A Barna Alpa / Anne Wheeler Inc. Production: "Diana Kilmury: Teamster", Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 24th Annual Labor Awards Honoring IBT General President: James P. Hoffa, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 60 Mimics 2 With Randy Credico: 37 min, Undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1994 Red Cross Disaster Stock Footage Reel, Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Actions Speak Louder Than Words: From IBT - Parcel + Small Package Trade Division Return To: George Kieffer, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - The Age of Wal-Mart, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - America on the Rocks, Undated; VHS cassette tape (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - American's Unions, Red Cross. Working Together to Save Lives time 12:06, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Baking Industry and Teamster Labor Conference: Route Driver Safety Training Program, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Ballad of Jimmy Hoffa" / "Lifetime of Forgettin'"; "Trucks Upon the Tracks"; "Song of the Teamsters' Union"; "Pledger of Allegiance" 2 of 2, Undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ben Robinson Jurisdiction: Reel 2 GBDIII, Undated; Magnetic reel to reel audio tape 7" 1200 ft. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Big Show Rough Cut, 1996 October 04; VHS cassette tape (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission: Meeting - Local 391 Special Convention: April 6, 2002 - Tape 2 -, 2002 April 06; Betacam video cassette tape (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Building a Better Future: Teamsters Joint Council 10 New England Delegates Conference February 1998, 1998 February; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Building FedEx, Building Our Union (9 minutes) [DVD], Undated; Series 3; DVD (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Building FedEx - Building Our Union (9 minutes) [VHS; 1st copy], 1997; VHS cassette tape (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Building FedEx - Building Our Union (9 minutes) [VHS; 2nd copy], 1997; VHS cassette tape (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Building FedEx - Building Our Union (9 minutes) [VHS; 3rd copy], 1997; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Building FedEx - Building Our Union (9 minutes) [VHS; 4th copy], 1997; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Building FedEx - Building Our Union (9 mins) [VHS; 5th copy], 1997; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Building Better Lines Through Political Action [Master Copy], 2001 June 19; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Bush White House: Inside the Real West Wing [NBC], 2002 January 23; VHS cassette tape (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Celebrating the new Atlantic City 20th Anniversary of casino gaming video news release, July 1997; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "China Trade Relations"; Inside Politics, CNN Cable and CNBC Cable, 2000 May 24-25; VHS cassette tape (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Christy Bailey "Talking about voting" interview #2, 7 September, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM SP video cassette tape (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CNBC's Healthy Solutions: Controlling healthcare costs, 14 February, 1998; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - CNN Brooks Jackson union dues checkoffs, 4 February 1998; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - CNN Lou Dobbs "America's Security Risks" "Rail", 8 February 2005; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - CNN presents w/ Aaron Brown: John F. Kennedy assassination, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Collectron of Arizona, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - A Commitment to Education, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Community Service: Red Cross Training in Puerto Rico (no audio for half of recording), 21 June 1996; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - "Complying with the new immigration law" Immigration and Naturalization Services Office of Employer and Labor Relations, Undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Coney Island Teamsters Rally - Tape 2 Cintas-Cincinnati, 2003 September 1; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Affairs - CONSSCO Finance Layoffs, Series 3; VNS cassette tape (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Creating a New Climate for Energy - U.S. Committees for Energy Awareness, Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - "CUTS" Greer, Margolis, Mitchell, Burns and Associates - AFL-CIO, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Dallas Cross Border Rally, 2001 March 5; Series 3; BETACAM SP video cassette tape (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Danger on the Rails: True Stories of American Train Disasters, 1995; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Delivering on Safety: How to Protect your Health from Chemical Spills - Our Rights Under the UPS/OSHA Agreement - IBT, 1992 September; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Diabetes Research Institute Dedication - Blueprint for Cure, 1994 February; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Diamond Walnut "Nutcracker Leafleting", Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Diamond Walnut #2, Undated; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Direct Line Motor Freight, CF Employee Communications Program, 1993 March; Series 3; VHS cassette tape (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Discussion on Striker Replacement IBT legislative Conference, San Francisco Reel 11 11:00:00, 1992 May 5; Series 3; Betacam Metal Tape (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Domestic Violence: Unions Respond Family Violence Prevention Fund, Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "Down Around Here" Wood's Diner Cambridge Massachusetts, 1978; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box Box 39, Folder 1)
  - "Driving America's Future" Teamsters/Drive, 2004; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Duet Communications AFL-CIO Convention Videos Global Solidarity, 1999; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box Box 39, Folder 3)
  - El Paso, Texas Texas Fair Trade Caravan, 1993 May 21; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - El Paso, Texas Rally NAFTA Protest Tape 1, 2001 February 16; Series 3; Betacam SP (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - El Paso, Texas Rally NAFTA Protest- Tape 2 Ruling to open boarder to unsafe trucks, 2001 February 16; Series 3; Betcacam SP (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - El Seguando- Fire Station Drills, Rescue, Equipment #1 LA, 1985 January 24; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Emery Worldwide :30 Teamster Commercial at 6:28 am ABC/NY, 1984 September 4; Series 3; Video cassette (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - EMS Worker Miami, Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 41, Folder 3)